1. openBrowser("")
5. setViewPortSize(1920, 1080)
9. enableSmartWait()
13. navigateToUrl(URL)
17. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
21. waitForPageLoad(30)
25. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"), 30)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. clickWhenReady("Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone")
1. obj = findTestObject(objectPath)
5. waitForElementPresent(obj, 20)
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)
6. saveHtmlSource("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. htmlPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().html
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. html = getHtmlSource(OPTIONAL)
2. println("Failed to save HTML source: " + e.getMessage())
9. println(Test Case '$testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()' finished with status: $status)